（忆往昔）
这些猎人已经失控了
These Hunters are out of control.
尤其是温家兄弟
The brothers Winchester, in particular,
而贝维尔夫人早已竭力阐明
which Lady Bevell has exhaustedly documented.
收服美国猎人的大实验
The grand experiment recruiting American Hunters.
失败了
has failed.
- 要我怎么做 - 铲除他们
- What would you like me to do? - Exterminate them,
一个不剩
Every…last…one.
那不是个孩子 那是路西法的后代
This is not a baby. This is the spawn of Lucifer.
- 小卡 - 不要
- Cass? - No!
我现在知道 这个孩子必须降生
And I know now that this child must be born.
并且保留他的法力
with all of his power.
海斯博士想了解一切
Dr. Hess wants to know everything.
温家兄弟的事
about the Winchesters.
抱歉我之前没接 我跟凯奇猎魔去了
Sorry I couldn't pick up before. I've been on a hunt with Ketch.
迪恩 我们有麻烦了
Dean? We've got a problem.
你在做什么
What are you doing here?
美国猎人完了
It's the end for the American Hunters.
但我可以保护你
But I can keep you safe.
只要你乖乖配合
if you play nice.
我从不会乖乖的
I don't play nice.
（如今）
狗狗乖
Good puppy.
[邪恶力量 第12季第21集]
妈妈
Mom?
Mom.
看来她有一阵没来这里了
Well, looks like she hasn't been here for a while.
嗯 她的东西都不在
Yeah. All her stuff is gone.
她有说她要离开这儿吗 还是
Did she say she was moving on or…
不 我把她的话告诉你了
No, I told you what she said.
她说「迪恩 打给我 我们有麻烦了」
She said, "Dean, call me. We have a problem."
然后就没了 她语气可不太愉快
And then that was it. She didn't sound happy.
好吧 她不在这里时
Okay, well, when she's not here,
就住在英国人那里 那或许
she's been bunking with the Brits. So maybe …
哥们 我给米克打六通电话了
Well, dude, I've called Mick, like, six times.
自从他被派去伦敦就一直杳无音信
He's been radio silent since they sent him to London.
凯奇 我想问问我妈是不是在你那儿
Ketch, calling to see if my Mom's with you.
是迪恩
It's Dean.
温彻斯特
Winchester.
就因为我想跟她说话
Because I'd like to speak to her, that's why.
不 我不是不耐烦
No, I'm not being terse.
如果你没见着她 你知道她在哪吗
Look, if you haven't seen her, do you know where she is?
不 我也没粗暴
No, I'm not being curt either.
我没工夫听你讲基本礼仪
Look, I don't have time for Manners 101 from you, okay?
如果她在你那儿 我想知道
If she's with you, I wanna know about it.
好吧
Fine.
混蛋
Such a dick.
- 怎么样 - 他说他一周多没见着妈妈了
- And? - He says he hasn't seen Mom in over a week.
但妈妈两天前才打来
But Mom called two days ago,
说在跟他办案
said she was working a case with him.
所以他撒谎了
Which means he's lying.
但他为什么要
But why would he …
乔迪
Jody.
乔迪 没 怎么了
Jody, hey. No, what?
没有
No.
- 我们没听说 - 妈妈吗
- No, we hadn't heard. - Mom?
什么时候 怎么回事
When? What the hell happened?
不 不 我…
Oh, no. No, I-I…
嗯 多谢告知我
Yeah, thanks for letting me know.
再见
Bye.
谁
Who?
艾琳
Eileen.
- 怎么死的 - 她…
- How? - She was, uh,
在林子里被一只野兽咬死了
mauled by a wild animal in a wooded area.
但那一带就没有那样的猛兽 南卡罗莱纳
that doesn't have animals that do that, in South Carolina.
她不是在爱尔兰吗
But I thought she was in Ireland.
萨姆
Sam…
迪恩 这是我们两周来
Dean, that's the second Hunter death.
第二起听闻的猎人死亡了
we've heard about in two weeks.
我知道 但两个不算规律
I know. But two doesn't mean a pattern.
三个就是了
Three would.
什么意思
Meaning?
妈妈也是猎人
Mom's a Hunter,
现在没人知道她在哪
and no one knows where she is.
干我们这行的人
People who do what we do,
你知道总会有人送命 但是
you know there are gonna be deaths, but…
这…
This…
这伤口
These wounds … I mean,
这么严重的我们也就见过几次
we've only seen something this bad a few times.
地狱猎犬
Hellhound?
对 但这毫无道理
Yeah. But it doesn't make any sense.
恶魔为什么要对她放地狱猎犬
Why would a … why would a demon sic a hellhound on her?
- 她又为什么离开爱尔兰 - 我不知道 迪恩
- Why did she leave Ireland? - I don't know, Dean.
好吧 算上艾琳
All right, well, counting Eileen,
那么三周里有七个猎人死掉了
that makes seven Hunters in three weeks.
嗯 这还是我们知道的
Yeah, and those are the ones we know about.
七起与怪物有关的死亡
Seven monster-related deaths.
怎么 外面那些怪物
I mean, what, did all the things out there.
突然开始合作了吗
suddenly start working together?
迪恩 怪物和恶魔不会联手
Dean, monsters and demons don't team up.
死了七个猎人
Seven Hunters are gone.
我们一直搜不到妈妈手机的信号
We can't grab a signal from Mom's phone.
小卡带着凯莉·克莱恩去了鬼知道哪里
Cass has Kelly Kline who knows where.
米克消失不见 凯奇在对我们撒谎
Mick has slipped off the grid. Ketch is lying to us.
我…
I-I…
我想揍点什么
I wanna punch something in the face.
很好
Good.
留着那股怒气
Hold on to that,
因为看来我们得对付一只地狱猎犬了
'cause it looks like we got a hellhound to deal with.
那么说
Which means…
我还要重复多少遍
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
给我找到凯莉·克莱恩
Find me Kelly Kline!
这个概念简直简单到可笑
As a concept, it's ridiculously simple,
你也一样
as are you!
请别吼我 我在尽力了
Please don't yell. I'm trying.
「我尽力了」 那再更努力点
"I'm trying." Well, try harder!
就好像你可怜的生命就指着它了
As if your almost-life depended on it.
是 吾王
Yes, my King.
说 你都知道什么
Bear down. What do you know?
我们知道大衮已死 不能保护凯莉了
We know Dagon is dead and can't protect Kelly.
那么你的任务该更简单了
Which makes your task even easier.
我们知道路西法的儿子就要生了
We know Lucifer's son is almost due.
那么你的任务就更重要了
Which makes your task more crucial.
我们知道 我们不知道他降生后会多么强大
We know we don't know how powerful he'll be when born.
那么你就是白痴了
Which makes you an idiot.
这我也知道
I know that, too.
看来 你和我派去执行这项任务的
Apparently, you and the legion of demons.
恶魔大军
that I've assigned to this task.
没有得到足够的激励
haven't been motivated properly.
- 跟我来 - 你要活剥我的皮吗 陛下
- Follow me. - You going to skin me alive, Sire?
那么简单还好了
Would it be that simple.
我要提醒你和你们那群废物
I have to remind you and your team of screwups.
优秀工作的骄傲
of the pride of superior work,
取悦我的兴奋感
the thrill of pleasing me,
以及多活一天的满足感
and the gratification of living one more day.
你好 里克
Hello, Rick.
玛丽
Mary.
请进啊 坐吧
No, please come in. Have a seat.
谢谢
Thanks.
你有我的地址
So you have my address,
- 但没有我的电话吗 - 一时兴起
- but not my phone number? - Spur of the moment.
有人说这附近有个吸血鬼巢穴
Someone dropped a dime on a vamp nest near here.
- 知道什么吗 - 我才听说
- You got anything? - No, news to me.
想加入吗
You want in?
嗯 当然
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
太好了
Great.
你怎么样
How ya been?
我嘛
Well, uh…
那群英国混蛋老来纠缠我
taking plenty of heat from the Brit Dicks.
让我加入茶点小队
to join the tea and crumpet squad.
他们可不愿接受拒绝
Yeah, they do not want to take "No" for an answer.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- Really? - Yeah.
- 要啤酒吗 - 好啊
- Want a beer? - Sure.
嗯
Yeah.
去他们的 是吧
I mean, screw them, right?
他们觉得都这么多年了…
What do they think, after all these years…
今天感觉如何
How are we doing today?
玛丽
Oh, Mary.
又出眼袋了
Those eye bags again.
昨晚发生什么事了吗
Did something happen last night?
能说具体点吗
Could you be more specific?
我离开这栋楼了吗
Was I out of this building?
那你该比我更清楚
Well, you would know that better than I.
除非你无法
Unless you're having trouble.
区分事实和虚幻了
distinguishing fact from fiction.
是这样吗 玛丽
So what's going on, Mary?
我没事
I'm fine.
是吗
Are you?
你在给我洗脑吗
You're brainwashing me?
你在被…重组
You're being…realigned.
很快 你将无法区分你自己和我们的想法
Soon, you won't differentiate between your thinking and ours.
你的想法和行为都将来自我们
All of your thoughts and actions will come from us.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
反正不是你抓着不放的对自己的错觉
Well, not about this illusion of you that you hold on to.
完美的生活
The perfect life.
有爱的丈夫和孩子
Loving husband and kids.
一切本就不完美 是吧
But it never really was perfect, was it?
你对你深爱的约翰隐瞒的那些秘密
All those secrets you kept from your beloved John …
你曾经的猎人生涯
that you were a Hunter.
亚撒色饶了约翰一命 作为交换 你允许他来
That you invited Azazel to visit when he spared John's life.
- 你怎么 - 我有眼线 玛丽
- How do you - I have sources, Mary.
到处都有
Everywhere.
你死后
After you died,
你挚爱的约翰为寻求复仇慢慢变得疯狂
your beloved John was a man slowly going mad, searching for revenge.
怎么 你儿子没告诉你吗
What? Your boys didn't tell you?
喝酒发狂 消失数周
The drunken rages? The weeks of abandonment?
真是虐待儿童
Child abuse, really.
怪不得他们那么…不健全
It's no wonder they're… damaged.
所以
So…
不再沉湎童话了
enough with the fairy tale.
我们要让你回归更纯粹的自我
We are returning you to a more pure version of yourself …
玛丽·坎贝尔 天生杀手
Mary Campbell, natural born killer.
不
No.
美国猎人没有如我们所愿乖乖合作
The American Hunters haven't fallen into line as we'd hoped,
他们要被清除
so they're being eliminated,
由我们的人铲除并顶替
repealed and replaced by our people,
你 玛丽
and you, Mary,
你要在其中扮演关键角色
you play a key role in that.
我不会的
I won't.
或许
Or…
你已经做了
maybe you already have.
有趣的选择
Interesting choice.
很快你将无法选择了
Soon you won't be making any.
下午好
Good afternoon.
海斯博士
Dr. Hess.
还是那么美丽
Stunningly beautiful as ever.
克劳力
Crowley.
还是那么虚伪得让人反胃
Revoltingly unctuous as always.
我们直说吧
Let's cut to it.
你在让你的人屠杀美国猎人
You have your people slaughtering the American Hunters,
不用说 这我支持
which, naturally, I applaud.
你知道这事
You know about that?
我给了亚瑟·凯奇一只地狱猎犬
I provided Arthur Ketch with a hellhound.
我猜他不是想要养宠物
I didn't think he was looking for a pet.
显然 你们组织是想在此扎根
Obviously, your organization is looking to put down roots.
我只是想确保你我之间
I just want to make doubly sure that you and I.
可以在美国延续
have the same arrangement in the States.
我们在英国的协议
that we do in the U.K.
没什么不可以
I don't see why not.
没必要开战 两边都不输
No point being at war. No sides lose.
如果你的恶魔只针对
If your demons limit their involvement.
那些愚蠢的 甘愿出卖灵魂的人类…
to humans idiotic enough to sell their souls…
- 没问题 - 信息共享呢
- Done. - And share information?
需要的时候
As needed?
我猜找到那个拿非利人是头等大事吧
I assume finding that infernal nephilim is a top priority.
鉴于它能杀了你 我 和整个宇宙
Since it could kill you, me, and the entire universe,
- 或许吧 - 我喜欢团队合作
- probably. - I am a team player.
我的恶魔这会儿正在全国搜索
My demons are scouring the country as I speak.
你注意到我的如释重负了吗
Did you notice my sigh of relief?
是啊
Oh, right.
我没有
There wasn't one.
克劳力 还有件事
Crowley, one more thing.
什么事
What?
你跟温家兄弟的关系
Your relationship with the Winchesters.
在我看来有点太亲近了
It's a bit cozy for my taste.
希望你不会指望我放过你的朋友
I hope you don't expect me to spare your friends.
我的检查结束了
That completes my examination.
德雷克索 我虽然很喜欢跟你一天天地
Okay, Drexel, as much as I enjoy playing doctor with you.
玩医生游戏 我需要马上离开这里
day after day, I need to blow this joint now.
请您耐心
I beg you to be patient.
我能关闭安保装置之前
Until I get the security device shut off,
你还是属于克劳力的
you completely belong to Crowley.
如果它法力已降至最低 而我又状态满格
Okay, if it's at minimum power, and I'm at maximum power,
我宁可一试
I'll roll the dice, man.
我说了 我毫不知情
I'm telling you, I don't know anything about it.
我完全没听过什么艾琳·莱希
The name Eileen Leahy means nothing to me.
克劳力 只有恶魔能控制地狱猎犬
Crowley, only a demon can control a hellhound,
那么 肯定跟你的人有关
which means that one of your people was involved.
如果是这样 我肯定会知道
If that were the case, I would know about it.
没有地狱猎犬失踪
There are no missing hellhounds.
我昨晚才抱过它们
I was cuddling with them just last night.
嗯 你也不知道
Right. And you know nothing else of.
其他猎人一个个死亡的事吗
the other Hunters who are dying?
我不仅不知道 还不关心
Not only don't I know, I don't care.
我没想到你还喜欢抱抱 克劳力
Never thought of you as a cuddler, Crowley.
多说说吧
Tell me more.
多说说
More?
我考虑了你的未来
I've been giving thought to your future.
作为我的奴隶 你可以当武器
As my slave, you could be useful as a weapon,
屠杀我的敌人
laying waste to my enemies,
首先就是某个英国贱人
starting with a certain British bitch.
动不动就对我下最后通牒
who's far too comfortable giving me ultimatums.
说完了吗
Are you done?
没有
No.
如果你知道凯莉·克莱恩
If you do have any information as to the whereabouts.
和你后裔的下落
of Kelly Kline and the spawn of your loins…
你最好是告诉我
…you may want to give that information to me.
我为什么要做那样的事
And why, oh, why would I do a thing like that?
因为 原来凯莉一直跟你的一个老朋友
Because turns out that Kelly's been chumming it.
混在一起
with an old friend of yours.
- 大衮 - 怎么
- Dagon. - So?
大衮死了
So…Dagon dead.
凯莉现在落入了
Kelly's now in the clutches.
温家兄弟的爱奴 卡西迪奥手里
of the Winchesters' love slave, Castiel,
他毫无疑问想让她死得很惨
who's no doubt dragging her to a gruesome death.
跟你计划的有趣的死亡不同
As opposed to the fun-packed death you have planned.
我的计划或许是救你儿子一命
My plan may just be to save your son's life,
把他当自己的养大
raise him as my own,
给他个机会用自己的力量为我效劳
give him the chance to use his power in my service.
我或许是你们父子活着相见的唯一希望
I may be the only hope you have of seeing him alive.
有意思
Interesting.
还是不了
Pass.
想想吧 时间不多了
Think about it. Tick-tock.
我得马上出去
I need to get out of here now.
我们刚又完成了一个疗程
We just completed another session.
她进展很不错
She's coming along nicely.
我知道你想让我加快她的进展 海斯博士
I know you wanted me to accelerate her progress, Dr. Hess.
我认为我做到了
I believe I've achieved that.
那是你叫我来的原因吧
That is why you brought me in.
对不起 你是指望
I'm sorry, were you expecting.
有人摸摸你的头吗 陛下
a pat on the head, Your Highness?
不 我才不指望你会那么斯文呢
Oh, no. I would never expect civility from you.
神经病
Psychopath.
你俩凑到一起真有趣
You two are such fun together.
当然 她或许要做你的手下
Of course, she may be reporting to you.
我不是个行政派
I'm not really an administrator.
你杀人不眨眼
You kill without mercy.
不会有问题的
You'll be fine.
瞧瞧你
I mean, here you are,
看着这女人受苦
watching this woman suffer.
几天前 你还跟她上了床
And only days ago, you were sleeping with her.
我当然知道
Of course I knew.
等美国猎人都被消灭
Once the U.S. hunters are gone,
我在认真考虑让你当家
I'm seriously considering putting you in charge.
太感谢您了
You're too kind.
当然了
Of course,
贝维尔夫人也很想得到这份工作
Lady Bevell is also desperate for the job.
对了
Oh, that's right.
你也跟她睡过
You slept with her as well.
嗯 多谢
Yeah. Yeah, no, I appreciate it.
谢了
Thanks.
我一直在到处打电话
So I've been calling around.
询问那些死去猎人的事
about all of the Hunters that died.
他们都经验丰富
Um, every one of them had years of experience.
我们有封艾琳的来信
We got a letter from Eileen.
艾琳
Eileen?
她四天前寄来的
She sent it four days ago.
她寄信是因为她觉得
It went snail mail 'cause she thought.
她手机和电脑都被黑了
that her phone and her computer were both hacked.
她离开爱尔兰是出于恐惧
She left Ireland because she was scared.
- 恐惧什么 - 她不小心杀了那个
- Scared of what? - Well, after she accidentally killed that …
英国哥们兰尼后
that Brit douche Renny,
她觉得英国记录者在追杀她
she thought that the British Men of Letters were on her.
「我知道他们在跟踪我 监视我
"I know they're following me, watching me.
他们窃听了我的手机
"They tapped my phone.
我在房间里发现了一个麦克风
I found a microphone in my room."
我也不想这么撒娇 但我能跟你们住几天
"I hate to be all girly, but I could bunk with you guys for a days.
直到事情解决吗「
until I sort this out""
你觉得英国人真在监视她吗
You think the Brits were watching her?
如果艾琳说是如此
If Eileen says they were …
那或许就是他们杀了她
Then maybe they're the ones that killed her.
你联络过的猎人
Those Hueners you were talking to,
包括泰瑞·马什吗
is one of them Terry Marsh?
嗯 密苏里州的泰瑞·马什 我找过他
Yeah, Terry Marsh in Missouri. I talked to him.
他也觉得
He, uh, he's also thinking.
杀人的不是怪物
it's not monsters doing the real killing.
好吧 我收到了他的短信
Okay, well, I got a text from him.
他一直在到处打探
He's been nosing around,
说是已经知道是怎么回事了
says he's got a fair idea of what's going on.
- 怎么 - 他不敢在电话上说
- And? - ‭He doesn't feel safe talking about it on the phone.
想跟我们见面
He wants to meet.
州际公路旁的老钢铁厂
The old iron works off the interstate.
明晚9点
Tomorrow night at 9:00.
他让我们停在路边的仓库旁
He says park off the road by the warehouse.
好
All right.
您逃跑的时机至关重要 吾王
The timing of your escape is crucial, my Lord.
如果装置损坏得不够
If the device isn't sufficiently impaired,
国王对您的控制只会加剧
the King's hold on you will only increase.
当然了 我也…
And, of course, I'll be …
我跟你讲清楚
Let me perfectly clear, okay?
我唯一的儿子有危险
My only son is in jeopardy,
而我要没耐心了
and I'm running out of patience.
再看看
‭Check it again.
这不可能
This…this can't be.
别告诉我它法力增强了
Do not tell me it's powering up.
- 是增强了 - 我叫你别那么说了
- It's powering up - I asked you not to tell me that.
但是反方向增强的
But in the opposite direction.
太不可思议了
This is amazing.
- 什么 - 那装置
- What? - ‭The device,
是直接与你的DNA
it's cemented directly into your DNA.
和国王的DNA融合的
and that of the King's.
它在你体内消减的同时
As it's powering down in you,
极性不知怎么逆转了
the polarity is somehow reversing.
说人话 德雷克索
English, Drexel.
控制权
The ability to control.
在转移
is transferring.
从克劳力到你
from Crowley to you.
你是说
So you're saying.
克劳力要变成我的小走狗了
that Crowley's gonna be my puppet.
乖狗狗
Good dog.
你为贝维尔夫人坐下了
You sat for Lady Bevell.
你怎么看得出
How can you even tell?
难道我要说「坏狗狗」吗
Am I gonna say "bad dog"?
他脾气可挺爆
‭He can be unpleasant.
海斯博士说你想谋
Dr. Hess says that you have designs on.
米克·戴维斯的工作
Mick Davies' job.
是吗
Did she?
她向我保证 会优先考虑我
She assured me it was mine to turn down.
有意思
Fascinating.
她对我也是这么说的
She told me the same thing.
好吧
Well…
让我们彼此对立 就像在肯德里克斯时那样
Pitted against each other, like our days at Kendricks.
我一直在那些情况下表现优异
I always did rather well in those situations.
你铲除对手
You slaughtered the competition.
有时候是真下杀手
Sometimes literally.
但我可没那么对过你 凯奇
And yet, I never slaughtered you, Ketch.
当时我们做爱很频繁嘛
Well, we were having a lot of sex at the time.
我研究美国的情况
I've been studying the American Situation.
以及如何治理好多年了
and how to fix it for years.
这份工作 是我的
So this? Is mine.
相信我
Trust me.
精英总能登顶
The cream always rises to the top.
这我同意
Oh, I agree.
凯奇先生
Mr. Ketch?
犯人要见你
The prisoner is asking for you.
自大的混蛋
Arrogant bastard.
贝维尔夫人 我有新消息
Lady Bevell, I have news.
我以为你不会来
I didn't think you'd come.
我快要疯了 凯奇
I'm losing my mind, Ketch.
我都不知道这是不是真的
I actually don't know if this…is real.
他们想要我做什么
What do they want me to do?
你已经在做的事 玛丽
Exactly what you're doing, Mary,
而且你做得很好
and you're doing it splendidly.
我杀了人
I killed somebody.
他是个朋友
He was a-a friend.
我经常那么做
I do it all the time.
我本来相信你们做的事
I believed in what you people were doing.
我跟你们一起作战 是希望我的儿子
I fought with you so that my boys could maybe.
或许能生活在没有怪物的世界里
live in a world without monsters.
你怎么能…
How can you just …
我不知道你指望什么
I'm not sure what you're expecting.
我插手吗
That I'll intervene?
我们说清楚了 我们又不是在恋爱
We made it clear to each other, we don't have a relationship.
我们一起合作
We worked together.
我们
We…
我们了解彼此
We know each other.
我并不了解你 玛丽
I don't know you, Mary. Not really.
你更不了解我
You certainly don't know me.
你不会想了解的
You…wouldn't want to.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
求你
Please.
玛丽
‭Mary…
别
‭No.
那你来
Then you do it!
杀了我
Kill me.
我这辈子 我所拥有的
All my life, all I ever had,
除了我的家庭
other than my family,
就是我的意志
was my will.
现在我要失去它了
And it's going away.
我在伤害别人
I'm … I'm putting people in danger.
我可能会伤害我的儿子
I'm putting my sons in danger.
你必须
You…have to…
求你
…please.
看在老天的分上
For God's sake.
杀了我
kill me.
- 玛丽 - 动手吧
- Mary. - ‭Just do it!
玛丽 听我说
Mary, listen to me.
就快了
It won't be long now.
这一切都会结束
This will all be over.
我保证
I promise.
- 不 - 我保证
- No. - ‭I promise.
不
No.
你再这样下去
You keep that up,
我们就得开始约会了
we're gonna have to start dating.
再过不久 我当然要除掉你
Before long, of course, I will get rid of you.
但我会怀念我们的闲聊的
But I will miss our little chats.
就是你就你想象的力量
Hmm, you mean the ones where you prattle on.
侃侃而谈 而我假装在听吗
about your imagined power, and I pretend to care?
那样的闲聊吗
Those chats?
小路西法怎么样了
How is Lucifer Jr.?
死了吗
Dead yet?
没有
Hmm…no.
还活着呢 健壮得很
Still alive and kickin'. Strong.
那孩子挺彪悍 我挺自豪
Kid's a bruiser. Sort of proud.
别急着订亲子课
Well, before you book a Daddy and Me class,
我要向你保证 你的王位不会有继承人
I must assure you there is no heir to your throne.
温家兄弟不会再搞砸了
The Winchesters wouldn't mess up a second time.
不好说 他们好像总是这样
I don't know about that. Seems to be sort of their thing.
他们以为又把我关回了笼子
I mean, they thought they would stuff me back in the Cage again.
但是 由于我机智 你坐在了这里
And yet, due to my cunning, here you sit,
完全受我意志的奴役
a virtual slave to my will.
如此自大 你和你的假儿子
And the hubris … you and your pseudo son?
简直痴心妄想
I mean, it's delusional.
虽然你
Despite your…
败得很惨
epic collapse,
却还是一直坚持幻想你能打败我
you persist in the fantasy that you will best me.
你的狂妄根本不能与我的妙计相比
Your bluster is no match for my masterful strategies.
说到底
And in the end,
你得承认 我
you have to concede that I have…
怎么回事
What's going on?
「妙计」
"Master strategist""
青蛙卡米特差不多
More like Kermit the Frog.
我的小木偶
Oh, my little Muppet!
克劳力 没有你我可如何是好
Crowley, what will I do without you?
你为什么监视我们
Why you spying on us?
你对艾琳·莱希知道什么
Oh, and what do you know about Eileen Leahy?
谁
Who?
你们的人
Did you … did …did your people,
杀了她吗
did they kill her?
可能吧
Probably.
经验法则 如果你觉得我们杀了谁
Rule of thumb … if you think we killed someone,
那八成是真的
then we probably did.
说起来 你们知道袭击我
Speaking of, you do realize that by attacking me,
就是招来了整个英国记录者的
you invite the retribution of the entire.
报复吧
British Men of Letters?
不必调查 不用审判
No investigation, no trial. Just.
直接惩罚毁灭
punishment and ruin.
可能是由玛丽·温彻斯特执行
Possibly at the hands of Mary Winchester.
那是什么意思
The hell is that supposed to mean?
你妈妈 成为我们的永久客人了
Your mother … she's our permanent guest.
她被你们囚禁了 为什么
She's your prisoner? Why?
囚禁 谁说我们囚禁她了
Prisoner? Who said anything about prisoner?
不 玛丽加入我们了
No, Mary's joined the team.
还有她自己的绝密解码戒指了
Even has her own super secret decoder ring.
你撒谎
You're lying.
是啊 没有戒指的
You're right. There is no ring.
男孩和妈妈啊
Oh, boys and their mums.
瞧 你们视她为妈妈
See, you see her as Mummy.
而我们视她为我们最好的杀手
We see her as one of our best killers.
就因为她跟凯奇合作
You know, just 'cause she works with Ketch.
不代表她喜欢他
doesn't mean she likes him.
或是你
Or you.
又被恋母情结蒙蔽了
Oh, that Oedipal myopia again.
你真觉得她跟凯奇
And did you really think she was just.
只是「合作」关系吗
"working" with Ketch?
那么多日日夜夜
All of those days and nights?
够了
That's enough.
他说有几次是他最棒的性经历
He said it was some of the best sex he'd ever had.
你要不要换个说法
You wanna rethink that?
好啊
Fine.
他说那一次是他最棒的性经历
He said it was the best sex he'd ever had.
迪恩
Dean, Dean.
- 好了 - 继续说
- All right. - Keep it up.
那米克呢 他扮演了什么角色
What about Mick? Where is he in all of this?
- 米克 - 对 米克
- Mick? - ‭Yes, Mick.
米克死了
Oh, Mick's dead.
他死了
He's dead?
是啊
Quite.
他被认为太重情义 不适合这份工作
It was determined he was too sentimental for the job.
原来 他太像你们
Turns out, he was too much like you two.
和其他美国猎人
and all the other U.S. hunters.
因此 这国家的每个猎人
Ergo, soon each and every Hunter.
也很快将跟他团聚
in this country will join him.
乔迪·米尔斯
Jody Mills,
克莱尔·诺瓦克
Claire Novak,
你们所有其他穿法兰绒
all of your other flannel-wearing,
喝威士忌的朋友
whiskey-swilling friends.
他们都死定了
They're dead.
嗯 感觉太棒了
Yeah, that feels awesome.
肌肉抽筋
Muscle cramps.
你知道好普拉提课程吗
You know a good Pilates class?
说清楚
So to be clear,
我接受你现在是老大了
I accept that you are now in charge.
我更喜欢这新的秩序
I-I like this new arrangement better.
你更多是个看大局的人
You're more the big picture guy.
而我则是管理日常杂物的
I'm the day-to-day minutiae…guy.
8号球 底袋
8 ball, corner pocket.
我可以这么玩一整天 但既然我是国王
Well, I could do this all day, but since I'm King,
什么的
et cetera, et cetera.
我来收个尾吧
I'll wrap it up.
你肯定知道这是迟早的
Oh, you had to know this was inevitable.
这要疼了
This is gonna hurt.
清理干净
Clean up on aisle 7.
听明白了吗
So we're clear?
你打给凯奇 告诉他 如果不想你死
You call Ketch, tell him if he wants to see you alive,
就给我们过来
he gets his prissy ass over here.
有趣的是 他已经来了
Interestingly, his prissy ass is already here.
贝维尔夫人 你能不能
Lady Bevell, would you mind.
解除他们的武器
disarming them?
- 起来 - 好了 凯奇
- Get up. - ‭All right, Ketch,
这里还有多少人
how many more guys are in here?
我们妈妈 她在哪
Our mom … Where is she?!
别动
Don't move.
说到就到
Ah, speak of the devil.
来得正好 妈妈
Perfect timing, Mom.
别动
Just stay where you are.
你听到了
You heard her.
我是说你
I was talkin' to you.
妈妈
Mom?
凯奇 别动
Ketch, stop.
最好别动 她会开枪的
I really wouldn't move. She will shoot you.
你妈妈一直是个厉害的猎人
Mummy always was a talented Hunter.
只是 对服从命令有点糊涂
Just somewhat…confused about obeying orders.
你把她怎么了
What did you do to her?
贝维尔夫人 让她不糊涂了
Lady Bevell cleared up that…confusion.
我想她已经告诉你们
And I suspect she told you that.
美国猎人都要死了
the American Hunters are a dying breed.
老天啊 你是想去哪
For heaven's sake, where do you think you're going?
- 凯奇 - 记得在肯德里克斯
- Ketch. - ‭Remember at Kendricks,
他们教我们 我们都是可以牺牲的吗
how they taught us that we were all expendable?
那不是闲谈
That wasn't idle chat.
妈妈
Mom?
看着我
Look at me.
是我们啊 求你
It's us. Please.
你是怎么了 妈妈
What's wrong with you? Mom!
你们的地堡真是绝佳的堡垒
Your bunker is an excellent fortress.
还是更好的坟墓
An even better tomb.
我们对锁做了改造
So we've rejiggered the locks,
切断了水
we've shut off the water, and.
等我们走后 抽入空气的泵
once we leave, the pumps that bring in the air.
会逆转
shall reverse.
你们的氧气会在
Your oxygen should be gone in…
两到三天内耗尽
two days, maybe three.
你们死在这里
You dying in here,
简直
it's almost…
有些诗意
poetic, hmm?
来吧 玛丽
Come along, Mary.
凯奇
Ketch! ‭
不
No!
他要求在他回来前收拾好
He wants this done before he returns.
那个我们怎么处理
What are we supposed to do with…that?
丢掉
Toss it.
贝维尔夫人真是厉害
I do have to hand it to Lady Bevell.
你的治疗
Your treatment's been.
到目前为止非常成功
most successful so far.
你要知道 这
And so you know, this.
会
will become…
越来越轻松
easier.
轻松
Easier…
伤害我爱的人会越来越轻松吗
to hurt people I love?
伤害你不记得你爱的人
Easier to hurt people you don't.
会越来越轻松
remember loving.
你有什么感觉
How do you feel?
挺好
Fine.
我挺好
I'm fine.
我的儿子
My son.